{
    "id": "ed1536fb8f924335a6672af3029bdaec",
    "title": "Determiners Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I could answer only ………………………. questions.",
            "description": "Few means almost none a few indicates a small number. ",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "a few",
                "a little"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a83bae0cc65f4070b52dd16d25da1957"
        },
        {
            "question": "She doesn’t have …………………………. friends in the city.",
            "description": "Not any means the same as no.",
            "answers": [
                "some",
                "any",
                "no"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6a76be84538946189a6811469bc16305"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………….. children like pet animals.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Most",
                "The most",
                "A most"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a0860330a9c04ab48cb890ac3b72f0d3"
        },
        {
            "question": "I haven’t got ………………………. money.",
            "description": "Use much with uncountable nouns and many with plural nouns. ",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "much",
                "more"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "110919d11f2145a9932c579353421531"
        },
        {
            "question": "I didn’t find ………………………….. there.",
            "description": "Not anybody means the same as nobody. ",
            "answers": [
                "somebody",
                "nobody",
                "anybody"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "97a2bc65d9d94ba3b45e7cf24c1b1594"
        },
        {
            "question": "There is ………………………….. to worry.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "nothing",
                "anything",
                "no thing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2e1cf6b63717411f8f8854a0adf1aa77"
        },
        {
            "question": "There are ……………………………. mangoes on the tree this year.",
            "description": "Use fewer with plural nouns and less with uncountable nouns. ",
            "answers": [
                "fewer",
                "less",
                "lesser"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ce6a8dcd15be4aafa8be23fd65a6130e"
        },
        {
            "question": "He earns …………………………. money than I do.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "less",
                "few",
                "lesser"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "72ff4f8b006540539b9bb1ef59a9ca5b"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has …………………………… confidence in her skills.",
            "description": "Use little with uncountable nouns and few with plural nouns. ",
            "answers": [
                "little",
                "few",
                "small"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2b2dabd959ca41a1b1ba76222cf76ff8"
        },
        {
            "question": "You have never given me …………………………… help.",
            "description": "Use any with negative expressions like never, hardly etc. ",
            "answers": [
                "any",
                "many",
                "some"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "966aad0f18704e179dc071888a29e6d2"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………….. of my friends are religious.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Much",
                "Most",
                "More"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "850903b21357429d8b0589d491b6863e"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. money has been wasted on that project.",
            "description": "Use much with uncountable nouns and many with plural nouns. ",
            "answers": [
                "Much",
                "Most",
                "Many"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "698534c1185f42f7a73d9a697874abae"
        }
    ]
}